// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Refers to an imaginary belt or circle in the sky that extends approximately eight degrees on either side of the ecliptic, which is the apparent path of the Sun across the celestial sphere throughout the year.",
    answer: "Zodiac",
    options: [
      "Constillation",
      "Astrology",
      "Zodiac",
      "Sign"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "They are known for their strong determination and stubbornness.",
    answer: "Taurus",
    options: [
      "Aries",
      "Gemini",
      "Taurus",
      "Capricorn"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "They have a strong presence and love being the center of attention.",
    answer: "Leo",
    options: [
      "Cancer",
      "Scorpio",
      "Leo",
      "Pisces"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Despite their confident and assertive nature, this Zodiac may secretly struggle with self-doubt and a fear of failure.",
    answer: "Aries",
    options: [
      "Aquarius",
      "Libra",
      "Sagittarius",
      "Aries"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "They are known for their sociable nature, but they may struggle with indecisiveness and find it challenging to commit to one path or choice.",
    answer: "Gemini",
    options: [
      "Gemini",
      "Cancer",
      "Leo",
      "Virgo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "They are known for their intensity and passion, but they may have a tendency to hold grudges and find it difficult to forgive.",
    answer: "Scorpio",
    options: [
      "Scorpio",
      "Pisces",
      "Leo",
      "Taurus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "It is a belief system and a pseudoscience that suggests there is a relationship between the positions of celestial bodies (such as the sun, moon, planets, and stars) and events that occur on Earth, as well as human characteristics and behavior.",
    answer: "Astrology",
    options: [
      "Hemisphere",
      "Constillation",
      "Zodiac Signs",
      "Astrology"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is often credited with the earliest known astrological practices.",
    answer: "Mesopotamia",
    options: [
      "Mesopotamia",
      "Constillation",
      "Astrological System",
      "Babylonians"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In Greek mythology, it is connected to the tale of the Golden Fleece. ",
    answer: "Aries",
    options: [
      "Capricorn",
      "Leo",
      "Aries",
      "Aquarius"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Known for their independence and rebellious nature, but they can also feel a deep longing for connection and belonging. ",
    answer: "Aquarians",
    options: [
      "Virgos",
      "Geminis",
      "Aquarians",
      "Leos"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];